Finding Aid for the SOUL Publications, Inc. records PASC-M.0342
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 2. Research Files, 1955-2002
  - Quincy Jones (folder 1 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 14)
    Includes a partial list of Soul articles about Quincy Jones; see also Brothers Johnson, box 56, folder 7
  - Quincy Jones (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1970-1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    See also Brothers Johnson, box 56, folder 7
  - Margie Joseph, ca. 1971-1978 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Julia (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Includes information related to the television series; see also Diahann Carroll, box 19, folder 16 and Marc Copage, box 20, folder 13
  - Ashley Judd, ca. 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - The Judds, ca. 1988-1996 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous K (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Eddie Kendricks, ca. 1968-1992 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Jayne Kennedy, ca. 1973-1983 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Chaka Khan (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Includes information about Rufus; see also Rufus, box 45, folder 3
  - Evelyn "Champagne" King, ca. 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1968-1978 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (folder 2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Eartha Kitt, ca. 1955-1978 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Gladys Knight & the Pips -- general (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1970-1986 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Gladys Knight & the Pips -- general (folder 2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Gladys Knight & the Pips -- Soul coverage (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Gladys Knight & the Pips -- press releases (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1972-1983 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Gladys Knight & the Pips -- press releases (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1972-1978 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Gladys Knight & the Pips -- Gladys Knight (Box 35, Folder 3)
    See also Pipe Dreams, box 41, folder 8
  - Gladys Knight & the Pips -- The Pips, ca. 1977-1980 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous L, ca. 1988-1997 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Labelle (folder 1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 7)
    Includes information related to the musical group featuring Sarah Dash, Nona Hendryx and Patti LaBelle; also includes information on their previous incarnation, Patti LaBelle and the Bluebelles; see also -- Sarah Dash, Nona Hendryx, and Patti LaBelle
  - Labelle (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1974-1978 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Patti LaBelle, ca. 1977-1997 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    Includes information related to solo career; for information relating to the group Labelle, see box 35, folders 7-8
  - Lady Sings the Blues (Box 36, Folder 1)
    See also Diana Ross, box 44, folders 6-8; Billy Dee Williams, box 52, folders 5-6
  - Little David Records, ca. 1973-1977 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Little Richard, ca. 1966-1997 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Darlene Love (Box 36, Folder 4)
    See also Phil Spector, box 45, folder 13
  - Mary Love, ca. 1966 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Lovelettes, ca. 1971 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Lovelites (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Love Unlimited, ca. 1972-1980 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    See also Barry White, box 52, folders 1-2; Love Unlimited Orchestra, box 36, folder 9
  - Love Unlimited Orchestra, ca. 1974-1979 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    See also Barry White, box 52, folders 1-2; Love Unlimited, box 36, folder 8
  - Cheryl Lynn (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous M, ca. 1987-1997 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Moms Mabley, ca. 1964-1976 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - The Mad Lads (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - The Manhattans (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Barry Manilow, ca. 1976-1980 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Teena Marie, ca. 1980 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    See also Rick James, box 32, folder 4
  - Marvelettes (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Barbara Mason, ca. 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Johnny Mathis (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1961-1987 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Johnny Mathis (folder 2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Curtis Mayfield (Box 37, Folder 4)
    See also the Impressions, box 31, folder 1
  - Alton McClain & Destiny, ca. 1977-1980 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Marilyn McCoo, ca. 1973-1981 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    See also Billy Davis and Marilyn McCoo, box 21, folder 5; Fifth Dimension, box 23, folders 1-2
  - Barbara McNair (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - MDLT Willis, ca. 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Harold Melvin & the Blue Notes, ca. 1975-1997 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    See also Teddy Pendergrass, box 41, folder 5
  - George Michael (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Stephanie Mills, ca. 1974-1980 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Miracles -- Smokey Robinson and the Miracles, ca. 1965-1976 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    See also Smokey Robinson, box 44, folder 2
  - Miracles -- "New" Miracles (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Includes information related to the Miracles with Billy Griffin as lead vocalist
  - Miracles -- Smokey Robinson, ca. 1972-1984 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Moments, ca. 1975-1980 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Also includes information related to Ray, Goodman, & Brown
  - Melba Moore (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Motown -- general (folder 1 of 3), ca. 1966-1984 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Motown -- general (folder 2 of 3), ca. 1966-1995 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Motown -- general (folder 3 of 3) (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Motown -- miscellaneous artists (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Motown -- Motown 25, ca. 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Motown -- Motown Revue, ca. 1985 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Motown -- Motown MCA (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Motown -- Motown/RIAA (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Motown -- Raynoma Singleton, ca. 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Includes information related to her book about ex-husband Berry Gordy and Motown
  - Eddie Murphy, ca. 1983-1997 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous N (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous O, ca. 1981-1995 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Bryan O'Dell, ca. 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Ohio Players (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - O'Jays (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Originals, ca. 1970-1981 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous P, ca. 1979-1997 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Ray Parker (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Freda Payne (folder 1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Freda Payne (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1969-1996 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Scherrie Payne, ca. 1978-1981 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    See also Freda Payne, box 40, folder 13 and box 41, folder 1, for fan club publications and articles relating to both sisters; also see the Supremes, box 47, folders 4-6 and box 48, folders 2-6
  - Peaches (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Includes information related to the all-female singing group, not to be confused with Peaches and Herb
  - Peaches & Herb, ca. 1968-1980 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Teddy Pendergrass, ca. 1974-1996 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    See also Harold Melvin & the Blue Notes, box 38, folder 2
  - Esther Phillips (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Wilson Pickett, ca. 1966-1975 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Pipe Dreams, ca. 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    See also Gladys Knight & the Pips, box 34, folders 4-6 and box 35, folders 1-3
  - Platters (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Pointer Sisters (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1973-1979 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Pointer Sisters (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1974-1996 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Bonnie Pointer (Box 42, Folder 1)
    See also Pointer Sisters, box 41, folders 10-11
  - June Pointer, ca. 1974-1983 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Sidney Poitier, ca. 1968-1977 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Billy Preston -- general (Box 42, Folder 4)
    See also Rolling Stones, box 44, folder 4; Syreeta, box 49, folder 3
  - Billy Preston -- newspapers, ca. 1968-1979 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Billy Preston -- press releases, ca. 1970-1977 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Prince (Box 42, Folder 7)
    See also Vanity, box 51, folder 6
  - Richard Pryor, ca. 1987-1996 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Q, ca. 1988-1995 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous R (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Raeletts, ca. 1969-1975 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    The group's name is sometimes spelled Raelettes, Raelets, or Raylettes; see also Sisters Love, box 45, folder 11
  - Otis Redding, ca. 1966-1979 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Vivian Reed (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Della Reese, ca. 1966-1978 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Martha Reeves, ca. 1966-1989 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Includes information related to Martha and the Vandellas; see also Motown, box 39, folders 1-6
  - Righteous Brothers (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Lionel Ritchie, ca. 1978-1996 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    See also the Commodores, box 20, folder 11
  - Smokey Robinson, ca. 1968-1998 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    See also Smokey Robinson and the Miracles, box 38, folders 5-7
  - Dennis Rodman (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Rolling Stones, ca. 1972-1979 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    See also Mick Jagger, box 32, folder 1; Billy Preston, box 42, folders 4-6
  - Room 222, ca. 1973-1975 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    See also Lloyd Haynes, box 27, folder 3
  - Diana Ross -- fan club (Box 44, Folder 6)
    See also Lady Sings the Blues, box 36, folder 1; Motown, box 39, folders 1-6; the Supremes, box 47, folder 4; The Wiz, box 53, folder 4
  - Diana Ross -- tour schedule, TV, and films, ca. 1969-1995 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Diana Ross -- 1999, ca. 1999 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - David Ruffin (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Jimmy Ruffin, ca. 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Rufus, ca. 1973-1979 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Includes information related to lead singer Chaka Khan; see also Chaka Khan, box 33, folder 9
  - Gloria Scott (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Shalamar, ca. 1980 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    See also Jody Watley, box 51, folder 20
  - Brooke Shields, ca. 1981-1987 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Shirelles (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Side Effect (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1975-1980 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Side Effect (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1975-1980 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Sister Sledge (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Sisters Love (Box 45, Folder 11)
    See also the Raeletts, box 43, folder 3
  - George Solomon, ca. 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Phil Spector, ca. 1975-1978 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    See also Darlene Love, box 36, folder 4
  - Ronnie Spector (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Spinners (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1973-1980 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    See also Philippe Wynne, box 54, folder 6
  - Spinners (folder 2 of 2) (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Edwin Starr (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Staple Singers, ca. 1965-1977 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    See also Staples, box 46, folder 5
  - Staples, ca. 1977 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    See also Staple Singers, box 46, folder 4
  - Candi Staton (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Sly Stone, ca. 1968-1978 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Donna Summer (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1974-1986 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Donna Summer (folder 2 of 2) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Sunday's Child (Box 47, Folder 3)
    See also Ren Woods, box 54, folder 3
  - Supremes -- general, ca. 1965-1990 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Primarily includes information about original lineup: Florence Ballard, Diana Ross, and Mary Wilson; see also Motown, box 39, folders 1-6; Diana Ross, box 44, folders 6-8
  - Supremes -- Jean, Mary, Cindy, ca. 1970-1976 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Includes information about second lineup, including Jean Terrell, Mary Wilson, and Cindy Birdsong); see also Jean Terrell, Mary Wilson
  - Supremes -- Jean, Mary, Lynda (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Includes information about third lineup, including Jean Terrell, Mary Wilson, and Lynda Laurence
  - Supremes -- Mary Wilson, ca. 1969-1997 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Supremes -- fan club (folder 1 of 3), ca. 1975-1983 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Supremes -- fan club (folder 2 of 3) (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Supremes -- fan club (folder 3 of 3), ca. 1975-1977 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    See also Scherrie Payne, box 41, folder 2 and Susaye Greene, box 26, folder 5
  - Supremes -- Supremes special, ca. 1976 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Includes information regarding the development of a special Supremes issue of Soul
  - Supremes -- reaction letters (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Includes letters written to Soul regarding the Supremes
  - Sweet Inspirations, ca. 1968-1975 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Sylvers, ca. 1973-1979 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Syreeta (Box 49, Folder 3)
    See also Billy Preston, box 42, folders 4-6; Stevie Wonder, box 53, folders 5-7 and box 54, folders 1-2
  - Miscellaneous T, ca. 1988-1996 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Bobby Taylor, ca. 1968-1976 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    Includes information about Motown artists Bobby Taylor and the Vancouvers as well as Taylor's solo career
  - Temptations -- general (folder 1 of 3) (Box 49, Folder 6)
    See also Dennis Edwards, box 21, folder 17; Melvin Franklin, box 24, folder 6; Eddie Kendricks, box 33, folder 7; David Ruffin, box 45, folder 1; Damon Harris box 50, folder 1; Otis Williams, box 50, folder 2; Paul Williams, box 50, folder 3; Motown, box 39, folders 1-6
  - Temptations -- general (folder 2 of 3), ca. 1968-1988 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Temptations -- general (folder 3 of 3) (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Temptations -- Damon Harris, ca. 1973-1979 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Temptations -- Otis Williams (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Temptations -- Paul Williams (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Temptations -- Temptations Miniseries, ca. 1998 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Tammi Terrell, ca. 1966-1975 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Philip Michael Thomas (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Also known as Philip Thomas
  - Three Degrees, ca. 1968-1997 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Toys, ca. 1966-1968 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Glynn Turman (Box 50, Folder 9)
    See also Aretha Franklin, box 23, folder 8 and box 24, folders 1-4
  - Ike and Tina Turner -- general, ca. 1966-1977 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    See also Tina Turner, box 50, folders 12-13; Mirettes, box 56, folder 15
  - Ike and Tina Turner -- Esquire "Ikette for a Night", ca. 1975 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Tina Turner -- general (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Tina Turner -- Tommy, ca. 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Leslie Uggams, ca. 1964-1977 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Undisputed Truth (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Also see Norman Whitfield, box 52, folder 4
  - Unifics, ca. 1970 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous V, ca. 1986-1996 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Luther Vandross (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Vanity, ca. 1982-1985 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    See also Prince, box 42, folder 7
  - Velvettes, ca. 1986 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Ben Vereen (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous W, ca. 1986-1997 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Lindsay Wagner, ca. 1976-1984 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Jr. Walker (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Barbara Walters (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Dee Dee Warwick, ca. 1967-1975 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Dionne Warwick -- general, ca. 1967-1995 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Also went by Dionne Warwicke
  - Dionne Warwick -- Burt Bacharach (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Dionne Warwick -- Tom Bell, ca. 1971-1976 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Dionne Warwick -- Bill Elliott, ca. 1974-1976 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    See also Bill Elliott, box 22, folder 3
  - Dionne Warwick -- in concert (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Denzel Washington, ca. 1989-1997 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Jody Watley, ca. 1987 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    See also Shalamar, box 45, folder 5
  - Raquel Welch (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Mary Wells, ca. 1968-1992 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Kim Weston, ca. 1967-1978 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Barry White (folder 1 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 1)
    See also Love Unlimited, box 36, folder 8; Love Unlimited Orchestra, box 36, folder 9
  - Barry White (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1973-1995 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Maurice White, ca. 1977-1980 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    See also Earth, Wind & Fire, box 22, folders 1-2
  - Norman Whitfield (Box 52, Folder 4)
    Also includes information related to Whitfield Records and the groups Rose Royce and Undisputed Truth; see also Yvonne Fair, box 56, folder 12
  - Billy Dee Williams (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1972-1980 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    See also Lady Sings the Blues, box 36, folder 1
  - Billy Dee Williams (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1972-1997 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Robin Williams (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Vanessa Williams, ca. 1984-1986 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Jackie Wilson, ca. 1979-1984 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Nancy Wilson (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - The Wiz (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Includes information on both the stage and screen interpretations; see also?
  - Stevie Wonder (folder 1 of 5), ca. 1967-1986 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Stevie Wonder (folder 2 of 5), ca. 1966-1985 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Stevie Wonder (folder 3 of 5) (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Stevie Wonder (folder 4 of 5), ca. 1967-1987 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Stevie Wonder (folder 5 of 5), ca. 1969-1996 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Ren Woods (Box 54, Folder 3)
    See also Sunday's Child, box 47, folder 3 and the Wiz, box 53, folder 4
  - Edna Wright, ca. 1977 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    See also Honeycone, box 27, folder 17
  - O.V. Wright, ca. 1974-1977 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Philippe Wynne (Box 54, Folder 6)
    See also Spinners, box 46, folders 1-2
  - Lena Zavaroni, ca. 1974 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Pia Zadora, ca. 1985-1987 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Vanna White (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Bette Midler, ca. 1987-1998 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Liza Minnelli, ca. 1987-1997 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Roseanne -- general (folder 1 of 3) (Box 54, Folder 12)
    Includes information related to the actress and comedian, also known as Roseanne Barr and Roseanne Arnold
  - Roseanne -- general (folder 2 of 3), ca. 1988-1995 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Roseanne -- general (folder 3 of 3), ca. 1991-1994 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Roseanne -- divorce (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Roseanne -- 1988-1990 (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1988-1990 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Roseanne -- 1988-1990 (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1988-1990 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Ricki Lake (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Matt Lauer (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - David Letterman, ca. 1988-1996 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Heather Locklear, ca. 1994-1998 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Lulu (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Greg Louganis (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Martin Lawrence, ca. 1997 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Joan Lunden, ca. 1992-1996 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Rob Lowe (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - John Branca (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - David Geffen, ca. 1990-1994 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Brothers Johnson, ca. 1977-1981 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    See also Quincy Jones, box 32, folder 14 and box 33, folder 1
  - Shorty Long (Box 56, Folder 9)
    Includes information about Motown recording artist Frederick Shorty Long; see also Motown, box 39, folders 1-6
  - Wolfman Jack, ca. 1977 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Gordy 1994 -- Taraborrelli research, ca. 1994 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    Includes list of titles recorded for Motown, Tamla, and Gordy record labels compiled by former Soul staffer, J. Randy Taraborrelli; see also Berry Gordy, Jr., box 25, folders 4- 8; Motown, box 39, folders 1-6 and box 40, folders 1-3
  - Motown 1994 -- Taraborrelli research (Box 56, Folder 12)
    Includes list of titles recorded for Motown and its related and subsidiary labels, including Soul, V.I.P., Mel-o-dy, Miracle, Rare Earth, MoWest, Melodyland (Hitsville), Chisa, MC, Prodigal, Natural Resources, Three Brothers, Manticore, and others
  - Yvonne Fair, ca. 1975-1977 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    See also Norman Whitfield, box 52, folder 4
  - Ahmet Ertegun, ca. 1986 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Jennifer Holliday (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Mirettes, ca. 1966-1970 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    Includes information on the group formerly known as the Ikettes; see also Ike and Tina Turner, box 50, folders 10 and 11
  - Minnie Riperton, ca. 1974-1979 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Funkadelic (Box 56, Folder 18)
- 3. Audio Cassettes, 1969-1980
  Audio cassettes, primarily of celebrity interviews for SOUL publications.
  - Smokey Robinson at the Century Plaza, 1969 February 24 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Mr. B #1 and Mr. B #2, undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Mr. B #3 and Sammy D. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Date pertains to Sammy D.; most likely refers to Sammy Davis, Jr.
  - Gladys Knight & the Pips, 1980 April (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Diana Ross Show Vegas, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Carolyn Franklin (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Sammy Davis Vegas, 1970 December 20 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    Refers to Sammy Davis, Jr.
  - B.B. King, 1970 January (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Cicely Tyson and Jamaica Film Festival (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Stevie Wonder, ca. 1960s (Box 57, Folder 10)
    Although date was included, the year is illegible. It appears to be from the late 1960s.
  - Gladys Knight & the Pips, undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Martha Reeves (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Sammy Davis, Jr. for Judy Spiegelman, 1980 June 21 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Lou Rawls at NBC and Lana Rawls, 1969 April 7 and 1969 April 14 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Lana Rawls (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Refers to the former wife of Lou Rawls
  - Belafonte and Tina Turner, undated (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - David Ruffin, first after leaving Tempts, 1969 January (Box 57, Folder 17)
    Refers to the Temptations
  - Stevie Wonder by L.P.J. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    L.P.J. is likely Leonard Pitts
  - Susaye Green, 1977 December 7 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Don Davis, producer (1 of 2), 1974 May 13 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Don Davis, producer (2 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Patrice Rushen by Mike Terry, 1978 October 23 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Natalie Cole and D.J. Rogers, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Donna Summer (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - King Hannibal and Damon Harris (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Rose Royce and Melvin Franklin and Isabel Sanford, 1978 December 6 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    Rose Royce is on side 1; Melvin Franklin and Isabel Sanford are on side 2; date pertains to Rose Royce
  - Quincy Jones by Phyllis Wickham, 1978 September (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Labelle splits by Vicky Wickham (1 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Labelle splits by Vicky Wickham (2 of 2), 1977 February 1 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Bill Cosby at the Disney Ranch by Donna Mungen, 1975 November 19 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Jim Brown (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Brick (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Archie Bell & the Drells by Ken Jones, 1976 April 7 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Maurice White, 1977 October 26 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Nipsy Russell/Wiz and Mabel King/Wiz (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Barry White (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Gladys Knight, 1977 January (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Mabel King "What's Happening" by Walter Burrell, 1978 July 18 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Hamilton Bohannon by Mike Terry (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Diana Ross (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Mary Wilson/Pedro Ferrer/Marco Turk (lawyer) by L.P.J., 1977 December 8 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Effie Smith funeral, undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Bill Cosby (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Eddie Kendricks leaving Tempts, undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Sammy Davis, 1970 June (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Scherrie Payne on South Africa (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - George Clinton and Gene McDaniels, undated (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Chris Beard, 1976 August 30 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Lola Falana by Ken Jones (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Formerly the Harlettes and Marvin Gaye by Leonard Pitts (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Isaac Hayes, undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Redd Foxx, 1976 April 7 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Redd Foxx quits and Aretha Franklin/Glynn Turman (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Gil Scott Heron (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Betty Wright and Beverly Johnson by Leonard Pitts, 1978 August (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - L.T.D. by Leonard Pitts, 1978 August (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - James Earl Jones (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Right on Time, R. Jones/S. Mills (Box 60, Folder 7)
    Refers to Regina Jones
  - Cicely Tyson, 1976 March 3 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Aretha Franklin, 1977 February 5 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Ronnie Laws and Stargard by Mike Terry (Box 60, Folder 10)
    Stargard is on side 1; Ronnie Laws is on side 2
  - Marilyn McCoo and Billy Davis, Jr. by Mike Terry, 1978 November (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Ohio Players by Marc Shapiro, 1978 November 21 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Tom Nemly on Black films (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Mandre interview and Christmas celebrity survey, ca. 1977 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Richard Pryor press conference and Danielle Spencer, undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Debbie Pryor (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Esther Rolle (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Jim Tyrrell, 1977 April (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Diana Ross by Leonard Pitts, undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Johnny Mathis and Deniece Williams (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Michael Schultz by Judy Spiegelman (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Tavares, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Sun and Three Degrees by Marc Shapiro, 1978 December (Box 61, Folder 6)
    Sun is on side 1; Three Degrees is on side 2